<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IMoguls</string>
    <string name="asiana_about">Located grandly amongst 2.25 acres of land of extraordinary beauty, whispering fountains and gleaming water bodies, the Kohinoor Asiana Hotel is a tranquil and lush oasis of immaculate pampering and luxury. With 178 elegant and well-appointed rooms and suites, Kohinoor Asiana is an epitome of luxury, comfort and relaxation. This 5 star corporate hotel in Chennai has remained the first choice of both business as well as leisure travelers in the city.\n
        The breathtaking surroundings, the high-end amenities and the unmatched hospitality offered by our diligent associates make it the ultimate destination to spend a few days during your trip to Chennai.\n
        Kohinoor Asiana is an ideal urban sanctuary, where the service is warm and amicable, the facilities are world-class, the cuisines are wonderful, and the guestrooms are roomy and welcoming. Kohinoor Asiana is home to classy dining outlets and a lounge that serves a variety of cuisines from different parts of the world and also gives you an opportunity to unwind after an eventful day. Our spa, swimming pool and fitness centre will definitely keep you engaged and rejuvenated. If you are planning a social or corporate event, we assure you that our state-of-the-art venues with all business-friendly amenities will help you make them a successful and grand affair.\n
        The convenience of the locale is harmoniously complemented by an exceptional style of personal attention, which is both impeccable and refined at our hotel making you feel right at home.</string>

    <string name="asiana_fnb_1">Caramel is our 24 hours open multi-cuisine dining outlet that serves delicacies from different parts of the world. With a capacity to host 102 guests at a time, the restaurant is known for its intricate decor and lively ambience. Although it serves all types of cuisines, it is chiefly famous for its Continental and Indian dishes.</string>

    <string name="asiana_fnb_2">Silk is our Thai and Indian specialty restaurant located at the lobby level. It serves authentic Thai food cooked by experienced culinary wizards from Thailand. We also offer an array of delectable Indian cuisines which will take you on an unforgettable culinary journey. Silk has three private dining rooms, and can host up to 68 guests. We believe in creating incredible dining experiences which is why live and soulful music accompanies good food here at Silk.</string>
    <string name="tahi">Thai and Indian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="asiana_fnb_3">It is our fine dining outlet that serves some of the best sizzling grills and steaks in the town. For unique dining experience, we have a live kitchen and two separate kitchens for both vegetarians and non-vegetarians. Our scrumptious and healthy grills include European, Mexican, Indian and Arabic delicacies.
*It is currently closed for renovation</string>
</resources>
